妈咪
Mommy!
他要来抓我了
He's gonna get me!
亲爱的 亲爱的 谁要来抓你
Honey, honey, who's gonna get you?
总统 我看见他了
The president! I saw him!
他要来抓我了
He's gonna get me!
克丽丝特尔 总统不会来抓你的
Crystal, the president isn't going to get you.
但我看到他了
But I saw him!
看到我说的了吧
See what I told you?
这就是她非要去的自由党学校
It's that liberal school she's going to,
看看都往她脑袋里装了什么东西
filling her head with all kinds of garbage.
亲爱的 总统在尽他所能地工作呢
Sweetie, the president is doing the best job he can.
你们学校只是
Your liberal school is just trying
想让你们相信他很危险
to convince you he's dangerous.
但 但是 爸爸 他要来
But... But, Daddy, he's gonna...
打住 到此为止
Unh-unh. No "Buts."
总统在白宫
The president is in the White House,
才不会跑来这抓你 好吗
not here trying to get you, okay?
-好吧 - 行了
- Okay. - All right.
我们明早得和学校谈谈了
We're having a talk with that school in the morning.
晚安 亲爱的
Goodnight, honey.
嘿 我的支持率如何
Hey! How are my approval ratings?
最新报道称
And the latest reports are now saying
超过一百万的加拿大人
that over a million Canadians
在核爆炸中丧生
were killed in the nuclear blast.
由美国总统下令投放的炸弹
The bomb dropped by the U.S. President
铲平了整个多伦多市
took out the entire city of Toronto
在未来几天里 核辐射尘预计会导致
and fallout is expected to kill thousands more
数千人丧生
in the coming days.
艾克
Ike.
艾克 对不起
Ike, I'm sorry that I...
是我导致加拿大遭到了核弹袭击
'caused a nuclear bomb to be dropped on Canada.
我只是
I was just...
我只是想
You know, I was just trying
叫停那个毒害大众的剧
to get shows that were toxic taken down.
你也知道那些剧真的害人不浅
You know, those shows can be really harmful.
噢 别假惺惺了
Oh, stop being a victim.
老天呐
Jesus Christ!
我想知道的是 谁给你的权利
What I want to know is what gives you the right
向我的孩子们宣扬你的政治观点
to preach your political views to my children?!
我的女儿晚上在噩梦中惊醒
Our daughter woke up with nightmares
就是梦到总统要来抓她
that the president was going to get her.
就算校长和副校长
Just because two liberals happen to be
碰巧是两个支持自由党的人
principal and vice principal
也不意味着你们可以给我的孩子们洗脑
doesn't mean you can brainwash my kids!
呃 我们现在面临着更大的问题
Uh, we sort of have some bigger problems
先生你是
right now, Mister, uh...
是怀特 鲍勃 怀特
It's White. Bob White.
你可能从未听说过我们一家吧
You've probably never even heard of our family, huh?
怀特家族从建校起就在这上学了
Well, the Whites have been here since the beginning!
那也不重要
Not that it matters.
因为没人关心怀特一家
'Cause no one cares about the Whites!
没错 每个人都有自己的麻烦
Sure, everyone else has problems,
但有人关心过怀特一家过得怎么样吗
but does anyone ever ask the Whites how they're doing?
怀特先生 我们向你保证 我们管理这所学校的
Mr. White, we assure you that we run the school
方式十分专业
in a very... professional manner
并且不会让个人情感
and don't let... personal emotions
影响工作
get in the way.
你们当然不会
Oh, sure you don't!
你们知道我费了多大劲
You know how hard I had to fight
才能来这和你们见面吗
to even get this meeting with you?
噢 是谁想和行政部门谈谈
"Oh, who wants to talk to the administration?"
噢 只是怀特一家吗
"Oh, it's just the Whites?"
谁管怀特一家怎么样 他们不重要
"Aw, who cares about the Whites? They're fine."
我们正打算把它
Well, we've just about had it you...
#如果爱你是个错 就让我错下去吧#
# If loving you is wrong, I don't wanna be right #
#就让我错下去吧#
# I don't wanna be right #
还有 该死的 我们被无视了
...and, damn it, we won't be ignored!
抱歉 有谁听到
I'm sorry. Is anyone else hearing
如果爱你是个错 就让我错下去吧
"If loving you is wrong, I Don't Want to Be Right"
非常非常小声
very, very quietly?
不是的 怀特先生和夫人
Uh, no. Mr. And Mrs. White,
我们保证我们不会让
we promise that we will not let anything happen
可能会使这所学校公正性遭到质疑的事发生
that might bring the integrity of this school into question.
我想怀特一家现在也就能这样指望了
Guess that's all the Whites can hope for these days.
嗨
Hey!
我的支持率如何
How are my approval ratings?
是总统啊
It's the president!
等等 回来 有什么问题吗
Wait, come back! What's wrong?!
总统仍没有
Still no word from the president
对他的贱番茄支持率跌到
as his 'Splatty Tomato' approval rating
前所未有的3%做出回应
drops to an unprecedented 3%.
这样 总统的支持率
This puts the president four points below
比抢劫坚果店2的票房还低了四个点
"Nut Job 2: Nutty by Nature."
同时 加拿大总理
Meanwhile, the Canadian Prime Minister,
贾斯廷 特鲁多号召加拿大人民要坚强
Justin Trudeau, called upon Canadians to stand strong.
毫无疑问 美国
Make no mistake, America.
如果你们不交出你们的总统
If you do not hand over your president,
就会发生你们前所未见的战争
there will be war the likes of which you have never seen.
加拿大人会团结起来
Canadians will rise together.
我呼吁海内外所有的加拿大人
I call on all Canadians here and abroad
和他们的国家同仇敌忾
to stand with their country.
美国总统必须为他的罪行负责
The U.S. President must answer for his crime.
只有加拿大能把他绳之以法
And only Canada can bring him to justice.
没事的 特维克 一切都会好起来的
There, there, Tweek. Everything is gonna be okay.
我知道我看到了什么 克雷格 你要相信我
I saw what I saw, Craig! You have to believe me!
怎么了
What's going on?
特维克急性焦虑症发作了
Tweek's having a panic attack.
是真的 他想要抓我
It was real! He tried to get me!
- 你说谁 - 总统
- Who did? - The president!
这只是你的想象 特维克
It's just your imagination, Tweek.
这不是他想象出来的
It's not his imagination.
我也看见他了
I saw him, too.
你也看到总统了
You saw the president?
在采石场外面 我当时还不敢相信
Out by the quarry, but I didn't believe it.
我想 这怎么可能是
I said, "How could this be..."
总统吗 我也看见他了
The president? I saw him, too.
他穿着一套蓝色的西装 还有一张屎黄的脸
He had a blue suit and an orange face.
他一直在问我 我的
He kept asking me, "How are my..."
我的支持率如何
"How are my approval ratings?"
我也看见他了
I saw him, too.
哥们 这些听起来是不是很耳熟
Dude, isn't this all really familiar?
我在那个叫怪奇什么的剧里
I saw something just like this
看到了类似的情节
on that show called "Stranger..."
怪奇物语
"Stranger Things."
怪奇物语是部剧 我也看了
"Stranger Things" Is the show. I saw it, too.
但等等 怪奇物语不就像那部电影
But wait, isn't "Stranger Things" Just like that movie...
就像电影小丑回魂
Just like that movie "It."
你也看了吗
You saw it, too?
对啊 我在电影院里看的
Yeah, I saw it in the theater.
我也看了怪奇物语和小丑回魂
I saw "Stranger Things" And "It."
天哪
Jesus.
我觉得大家都没有胡说
I don't think anyone's imagining anything.
我觉得总统就在这
I think the president is here.
孩子们进屋去
You kids get inside somewhere.
我得去提醒镇上的人
I have to warn the town.
好了 大家 大家 安静
All right, people. People, please.
我们需要大家都努力保持冷静
We need everyone to try and stay calm.
总统在这吓唬我们的小孩
How can we stay calm when the president's
我们要怎么冷静
out there scaring our children?!
听着 我们都想让总统离开这里
Look, we all want the president out of here.
现在就是我们要怎么做的问题
It's just a matter of how we do it.
我知道你们都想摆脱他
I know you all want to get rid of him.
这不对
That's not true.
怀特一家还支持着总统
The Whites still support the president!
得了吧 怀特 他四处乱跑
Oh, for sake, White, he's running around
吃我们的宠物 恐吓我们的孩子
eating our pets and terrorizing our kids!
你觉得希拉里会做得更好吗
You think Hillary would have been any better?
坐下吧 鲍勃
Just sit down, Bob!
我只是说说而已 说说而已
I'm just sayin'! I'm just sayin'!
大家听着 我现在有一组人
Listen, everyone. I have a team right now
在尝试确定总统的位置
that's trying to locate the president,
我希望你们能听领导这次搜寻行动的
and I'd like you to hear from Officer Bright,
布莱特警官说几句
who's leading the search.
大家好 我们知道你们都很关心
Hey, folks. We know you're all concerned,
但我想向你们保证 我们在尽我们所能
but I want to assure you that we are doing everything we can
追查总统的下落 并且让他安全地离开
to track the president down and have him safely removed.
自从总统的支持率这么差以后
Since the president was given a splatty tomato,
他就变得非常危险且不顾一切
he's become very desperate and very dangerous.
如果你看到总统 不要接近他
If you see the president, do not approach him.
不要和他理论
Do not try to reason with him.
最重要的是要记住 这可是总统
Most importantly, remember that this is the president,
你不能开枪去打他 好吗
so you cannot shoot him. All right?
连讲都不要讲
You can't even talk about shooting him.
甚至都不要
Don't even...
做一些要击杀他的讽刺的举动
do any coy satirical takes on shooting him.
好的
Okay, good.
我们想要做的
What we're trying to do here
只是把总统赶走
is just get the president to go away.
我们会给你们发放这样的锁
We're gonna be handing out padlocks like this one
这样每个人都可以把自己的车库锁起来
so everyone can lock up their garbage.
如果我们不给总统食物 他应该会走掉的
If we don't feed the president, hopefully he'll just move on.
有什么问题吗
Are there any questions?
我们可以用一种略带讽刺的方式
Can we talk about a friend shooting him
和朋友讨论击杀他的事情吗
if it's in a sort of a sarcastic way?
不不不 现在最好是
No, no, no. Now, it's - it's just best
干脆不要谈论这样的事情了
to avoid that kind of talk altogether.
记住 他们可以对凯西 格里芬做什么
Remember, they can do to you
也可以对你们做什么
what they did to Kathy Griffin.
让她30年不能再搞笑了
Made her not funny for 30 years?
没错
That's right.
所以最好的办法就是把车库锁起来
So best thing is just lock up your garbage
然后看看总统会不会离开
and see if we can get the president to go away.
天哪
Jesus.
现在孩子们开始不见了
Now kids are going missing.
不久我们都会不见的
We're all gonna be missing soon!
凯尔
Kyle!
都是我的错
It's my fault.
艾克想要自己把事情摆平
Ike went to go take matters into his own hands.
我必须要去找他
I have to find him.
我们会帮你的
We'll help you.
我们都会帮你的
We'll all help you.
大伙 这是相当危险的事情啊
Guys, this could be really dangerous.
你不许去
You're not going.
你答应过我 今天晚上我们要约会的
You promised tonight we'd have a date night.
亲爱的 这比约会之夜更紧急啊
Darling, this is a little more pressing than date night.
哦 好吧
Oh, great.
也就是说 凯尔的笨蛋兄弟消失了 而我
So, Kyle's stupid brother goes missing, and I get
我怎么总是卷在这种破事里面
How come I'm always the one getting shit on around here?
你们谁都别跟我去
I don't need anyone to go with me.
哦 怎么了 凯尔
Oh, what's the matter, Kyle?
不想要我一起去
Don't want me around because
因为你喜欢我而我拒绝了你吗
you had the hots for me and I shut you down?
我绝不会喜欢上现在的你了
I would never ve the hots for the person you are now.
拜托了 各位
Come on, you guys.
听着 我们都知道现在要做什么了
Look, we all know what we're supposed to do now.
我们都看见过 小丑回魂 还有 怪奇物语
We all saw "It" And "Stranger Things."
我们要背上包包进到森林里
We need to get our backpacks and go out to woods
把咱镇从那个恶魔 还有80年代音乐中救出来
and save the town from evil to some kick-ass '80s' music!
你好啊 今天中午要在我们这吃饭吗
Hello, joining us for lunch today?
是的
Uh, yes.
我们是带今日的优秀学生来
We are here with our student of the day
与校长和副校长一起吃午餐的
to reward him lunch with the principal and vice principal.
我们有预约
We have a reservation.
好的 请问您姓什么
Okay, last name?
女
Woman.
名字呢
First name.
强人
Strong.
哦 有的 女强人
Oh, yes, Strong Woman, here we are.
我们为你预备了很好的座位
We have a nice booth set up for you.
我们不能继续下去了
We can't keep doing this.
人们会看出来的
People are gonna see through it.
难道在工作中
Is it my fault that I found
找到最棒最完美最美丽的女人
the most amazing, perfect, beautiful woman...
是我的错吗
at work?
没人会懂的
Nobody will understand.
或许他们会的
Maybe they will.
我们是坠入爱河的同事
We're co-workers who are in love.
你真的觉得这对其他人有影响吗
You really that's going to bother people?
额 我们要开始点餐了吗
Well, should we order now?
鲍勃 你在干什么
What are you doing, Bob? Aah!
你是在故意把食物拿出去吸引总统吗
Have you been putting food out for the president?
不 我只是 额
No, I was just, uh,
把这些手指三明治扔掉
taking these finger sandwiches to the trash.
我们都同意不要喂他 这样他就会离开
We all agreed not to feed him so he'd go away.
不是全体都同意了 是你们同意的
We didn't all agree! You all agreed!
没人问过怀特家的想法
Nobody asked the Whites how they felt!
没人会在意怀特家会怎么说
Nobody cares what the Whites have to say!
鲍勃 拜托
Bob, come on.
你要知道他待在这里对我们很不安全
You have to know it's not safe to have him here.
2003年的时候 希拉里 克林顿
In 2003, Hillary Clinton admitted
挪用了外交官的基金
to taking funds for her foundation
转入自己的基金会
from foreign diplomats!
拜托 这两者之间有什么联系吗 鲍勃
What's that got to do with anything, Bob? Come on.
这是真的
It's true!
鲍勃 如果加拿大发现总统藏在这里
Bob, if Canada finds out the president is hiding here,
他们会用核弹攻击我们的
they are going to nuke us.
他必须离开
He needs to go.
希拉里当了总统也不会好到哪儿去
Hillary wouldn't have been any better.
把手指三明治给我
Give me the finger sandwiches.
好吧
Fine!
就这样 把怀特的三明治带走吧
Go ahead and take the White's sandwiches!
反正他们都把所有东西带走了
They've taken everything else!
我们是芝加哥熊队跳鬼步
# We are the Bears shufflin' through #
为了你 跳鬼步
# Shufflin' on down, doin' it for you #
我们很坏 但是我们知道自己是好意
# We're so bad we know we're good #
像计划好的一样刷新你的三观
# Blowin' your mind like we knew we would #
我们来就是为了制造麻烦
# We're not here to start no trouble #
我们只是在跳超级碗鬼步舞
# We're just here to do the Super Bowl shuffle #
兄弟们 这是80年代的音乐吗
Dude, this is '80s' music?
是的 这是潘多拉 是80年代的频道
Yeah. It's Pandora. '80s channel.
跳下一首吧 兄弟
Well, just skip to the next song, man.
我们想要振作起来 消灭恶魔
We're trying to get psyched to destroy evil.
我们需要更好一些的80年代音乐
We need better '80s' music than that.
歌莉娅
# Gloria #
你总是在追求
# You're always on the run now #
追求某人
# Running after somebody #
你总会得到他的
# You gotta get him somehow #
我觉得你要慢一些
#I think you've got to slow down #
海蒂 宝宝 你在干什么
Heidi. Honey, what are you doing?
这里是
This is the place...
这里是我终结一切的地方 记得吗
This is the place where I ended it all, remember?
我把手机从这座桥上扔下去
This is where I threw my phone off the bridge
然后永远退出了推特
and quit Twitter for good.
我曾经那么不同
I was so different then...
那么天真 充满希望
so naive and hopeful.
是的 甜心 现在我们可以继续走了吗
Yes, honey, now, can we get going, please?
抱歉 让我一个人静静
I'm sorry! I'm trying to have a moment here!
这里是我们开始的地方 你这个混蛋
This is where our whole relationship started, asshole!
是的 甜心 这很感人
Yes, it's very touching, sweetheart.
我非常的爱你
I love you so much.
我很抱歉 伙计们
I'm sorry about this, you guys.
我想起了孤单的日子
I remember feeling like I had nobody.
瘦瘦的我
Skinny bitch.
我们要继续走了 大家
We need to keep going, guys.
别告诉我你还没把总统弄走
Don't tell me you haven't gotten the President out of here.
我们还没把总统弄走
We haven't gotten the President out of here.
还有一些更坏的消息
And there's some worse news.
一群孩子消失了
A bunch of kids have gone missing.
- 什么 - 我觉得我们必须要假设
- What? - I think we have to assume
总统已经 把他们吃掉了
that the President has... eaten them.
为什么你还在这里和我说话
Why are you here talking to me
不是应该去找一下总统吗
instead of trying to find the President?!
别担心 快找到了 他就在树林里的某处
Don't worry, we're close. He's out in the woods somewhere.
而且我们设置了一个 福克斯 陷阱
And we've set up a fox trap.
一个 福克斯 陷阱
A fox trap?
福克斯新闻
Oh, Fox News...
他们会听我讲话的
They'll listen to me.
他们会洗白我的
They'll get my side of the story right!
这是个陷阱
It's a trap!
什么
What?
这是个福克斯陷阱 总统先生
It's a Fox trap, Mr. President!
哦 多亏了怀特一家
Oh, thank God for the Whites...
在这样的夜里 艾克 艾克
# Hold on to the nights # Ike! Ike?!
在这样的记忆里
# Hold on to the memories #
兄弟 拜托 这不是最棒的80年代的音乐
Dude. Come on! This is not kick-ass '80s music!
在这样的夜里 理查 马克斯 1988年
"Hold On to the Nights" Richard Marx. 1988.
我们真的需要音乐吗
Do we really need music?
是的 克雷格用错软件了
Yeah! Craig just has the wrong stuff.
别用潘多拉了 我要用Spotify
Forget your Pandora. I'm doing Spotify.
80年代音乐 好了
'80s music. 'Kay. There.
我爱吃豆人 吃豆人
# I've got Pac-Man fever # # Pac-Man fever #
没错 这样好多了
Oh, yeah. That's better.
我们能走了吗
Can we go please?!
我为吃豆人发狂 吃豆人
# I've got Pac-Man fever # # Pac-Man fever #
我快要疯了
# I'm going out of my mind #
快要疯了
# Going out of my mind #
就是这里
Here it is.
艾克
Ike?
等等
Wait a minute...
这不是之前你带我来的地方吗
Isn't this the place you brought me before?
你说你朋友
The place you said your
砸了你的电话和电脑的地方
friends smashed your phone and computer...?
我记得我还为你感到难过
I remember I felt so bad for you.
我们过去常常坐在公园里聊上几个小时
We used to sit in the park and talk for hours.
为什么我们再也不这么做了
How come we never do that anymore?
我们走吧
Oh, . Here we go.
去干吗
Here we go what?!
你以前对我很好
You used to be so nice to me.
You used to be nice to me!
我尽力了
I tried!
但是每次我要跟你谈谈的时候
But then you started rolling your eyes
你眼睛就开始乱转
- every time I tried to talk to you! - Ughhh...
他也不在这里
He's not here either.
兄弟 也许你弟弟
Dude, maybe your brother
根本没有去找总统
Didn't even go looking for the President.
你不了解加拿大人
You don't understand Canadians.
他们对自己的国家很忠诚
They're fiercely loyal to their country.
当加拿大被攻击了 他们都会为国而战
When Canada is attacked, they all join in the fight.
兰迪 兰迪
Randy! Randy!
- 怎么了  - 他们发现他了
- What? - They got him!
他们发现总统了
They found the President!
我们找到了他的藏身之处 那里
We found his hideout. There.
总得有人去把他赶出来
Someone's gotta go flush him out.
我会做好陷阱抓他
I'll be ready to trap him.
我去吧
I'll do it.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey!
记住他一直吃动物
Just remember he's been eating animals
像个野兽一样活着
and living like a monster. Just...
为你要看到的东西做好准备
prepare yourself for what you're out to see.
天啊
Oh, my God!
什么鬼 校长和副校长
What the... Principal and Vice Principal...?
我告诉过你我们藏不住的
I told you we couldn't hide.
但是
But...
但是你们俩一起工作
But you two work together...
你们两个一起工作
You two work togeth...
嘿 到底怎么回事
Hey, what the hell's going on?!
他们在一起了
They're together!
谁在一起了
Who's together?
校长和副校长
The Principal and the Vice Principal!
他们不能在一起 他们是同事
They can't be together! They're co-workers!
等等 你是说他是她的上级
Wait, wait. You mean he's actually her superior
然后他们在那里
and they were in there...
谁会想把自己的小弟弟放进同事身体里
Who would want to put their penis in a co-worker?!
玩弄红心皇后
# Playing with the Queen of Hearts #
知道她不是真的聪明
# Knowing it ain't really smart #
小丑不是唯一的傻瓜
# The Joker ain't the only fool #
谁会愿意为你做任何事
# Who'll do anything for you #
哦 天啊 看
Oh, my God! Look!
铺设另一个谎言
# Laying out another lie #
这是他的玩具望远镜
These are Ike's toy binoculars!
他在这里
He was here!
艾克
Ike!
这个地方我也记得
I remember this place too...
万圣节的时候你带我来过这里 记得吗
This is where you brought me on Halloween. Remember?
记得 亲爱的 那不浪漫吗
Yes, darling, wasn't it romantic?
不 一点都不浪漫
No! It wasn't romantic.
那时有个女巫 你让我打扮的像格雷特尔
There was a witch and you had me dress up like Gretel and...
你差点害死我
you were trying to get me killed!
亲爱的 你让我在南瓜园里迟到了 记得吗
Sweetheart, you made me late to the pumpkin patch, remember?
- 我很受伤 - 你很受伤
I was hurt. You were hurt!
你是受害人
You were the victim.
我很高兴你明白了
I'm glad you understand.
谁把你变成了这样 海蒂
Who turned you into this, Heidi?
闭嘴 皮包骨屁股的小贱人
Shut up! Skinny-ass bitch!
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything!
海蒂 我觉得在树林里诡异的散步
Heidi, I think spooky walk in the woods
让你有点失去理智了
is making you lose it a little bit.
各位
Guys!
我严重脱水而且要饿死了
I'm seriously dehydrated and starving.
我受够了这鬼地方
I'm pretty sick of this shit,
所以你最好   啊
so you better... Aah!
我们已经搜查过这片地方了吗
Have we already done a search of this area?
也许是海蒂跟她男票一起去的
Maybe Heidi went there with her boyfriend!
她现在应该会打电话来
She would have called by now.
我刚跟麦考密克谈过了
I just talked to the McKormicks.
他们从昨天起就没见过特维克和克雷格
They haven't seen Tweek or Craig since yesterday.
兰迪
Randy!
你有什么发现吗
Did you find anything?
莎伦 我 我
Sharon... I-I...
怎么了 你发现了什么
What is it? What did you find?
那 那里
The... There's... Ugh...
告诉我 你得告诉我
Tell me! You have to tell me!
哦 天啊 你看到了什么
Oh, God. What did you see?!
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
你快告诉我 我能接受
You have to tell me! I can take it!
你找到我们儿子的胳膊了吗
Did you find our son's arm?
你发现他四分五裂了吗 怎么了
Did you find him torn apart? What?!
校长和副校长 好像 在一起了
The Principal and Vice Principal are, like... together.
是总统
It's the President!
艾克 凯尔
Ike! Kyle!
斯坦 你没事
Stan, you're okay!
对 我们没事
Yeah, we're okay!
我们找到他了 我们找到这个小贱人了
We got him. We got the son of a bitch.
退后
Get back!
大家退后 现在 快过来 家人们
Everyone back! Do it now! Get over here, family!
鲍勃 我天啊 我们的国家要陷入战争了
Bob, for the love of Pete, our country is about to go to war!
你想知道哪里有战争吗
You wanna know where there's a war?!
圣诞节有一场战争
There's a war on Christmas!
没人关心那个
Nobody cares about that!
猜猜谁喜欢圣诞节
'Cause guess who loves Christmas.
怀特一家
The Whites!
至少这个男人想拯救圣诞节
At least this man's trying to save Christmas!
没错
That's true!
他不是在拯救圣诞节 鲍勃
He's not saving Christmas, Bob.
他到处乱跑 吓唬你的孩子们
He's running around, scaring your kids,
在树林里拉屎
and shitting in the woods.
拜托 鲍勃
Come on, Bob.
什么对你女儿最好 我是说 真正的
What's best for your daughter? I mean, really?
你就是一坨屎 这都是你的错
You piece of shit! This was all your fault!
你操控了我
You controlled me and manipulated me
把我变成这样
and turned me into this!
宝贝 把枪放下 好吗
Baby, put down the gun, sweetheart, okay?
我以前很善良  我以前富有同情心
I used to be kind. I used to be caring.
但是之后你 你
But then you... you...
不 不是你
No. Not you.
是我 我的错
Me. I did this.
我当受害者当成了一种生活方式
I let being a victim become a way of life.
如果你总是以为自己是受害者
If you always make yourself the victim,
那就证明你是很糟糕的
you can justify being awful.
埃里克
Eric...
对不起
I'm sorry.
我要跟你分手
I'm breaking up with you.
亲爱的 别搞笑了
Honey, don't be ridiculous.
我以前很可笑
I've been ridiculous.
我必须学会停止为自己感到难过
I have to learn to stop feeling sorry for myself.
海蒂 你不能跟我分手
Heidi, you are not breaking up with me.
不 我可以 我们之间结束了
Yes, I am. It's over.
我恐怕不能让你那么做 亲爱的
I'm afraid I can't let you do that, sweetheart!
后退 我会这么做的 我发誓
Step back! I'll do it! I swear to God!
这次不管用了 埃里克
It's not gonna work this time, Eric.
你跟我分手 我就自杀
You break up with me, I will kill myself!
这是你的选择 海蒂
The choice is yours, Heidi!
快点 各位
Come on, everybody!
埃里克 我们不想让你死
"Eric, we don't want you to die."
对不起
I'm sorry.
你可以做受害者
You can be the victim.
我不行
I can't.
海蒂
Heidi!
海蒂 我会开枪的 动手了
Heidi, I'm gonna do it! Here we go!
海蒂 你真的
Heidi?! Are you seriously...
他挣脱了绳子
He broke free.
总统又逍遥法外了
The president is on the loose again.
他现在更绝望了
He'll be even more desperate now.
情况变的更糟糕了
It's going to get worse.
我们毁不了他 对吗
We can't destroy him, can we?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想
I guess...
这取决于怀特一家
it's up to the Whites.
谁会把他们的小弟弟放同事身体里
Who would want to put their penis in a co-worker?!